steelguru.com 2013-05-18

# privacy policy, steelguru policy, steelguru privacy, steel guru

Major & Minor Exims Pvt Limited ("we", "us" or "our") is committed to protecting your privacy and providing a service that is safe and powerful. This Privacy Statement applies to www.steelguru.com (hereinafter the "Site") and governs data collection and usage arising in respect of the Site and the associated services. By accessing and using the Site and our services, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

Use of your Personal Information 

Personal information provided by you as part of the subscription process, or otherwise, is used to operate the Site, manage your subscription and deliver the services you have requested. We also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of important changes to the Site and its functionality, other products or services available from our affiliates and us and, from time to time, to contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. You can choose to not receive information about third party products and services when registering with the Site. If you initially chose to receive this information and no longer wish to do so you should log into the Site and choose the appropriate options. Alternatively please email us at [ info@steelguru.com ](mailto:info@steelguru.com). 

We do not sell, rent, lease make available to or otherwise distribute customer lists to third parties and in no circumstances will your unique personally identifiable information (including your e-mail, name, address, telephone number) be transferred to a third party, unless you give us specific authority to do so. 

We keep track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit via or within the Site, in order to determine which of our sites and services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising. 

When you enter our Site, we use your Internet Protocol (hereinafter ) address to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer the Site and to help identify you. We also have the ability to know what type of operating system and browser software you use and to identify the geographical location of your browser. To gather broad demographic information and for other purposes, such as monitoring visitor frequency, we also use your IP address. We may share certain information we gather with advertisers and other partners. The information we share comprises information in aggregate form only. We do not share personal information about anybody unless we have your specific permission to do so. 

We may disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith believe that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on us or the Site;   
(b) protect and defend our rights or property. 

Voluntary Information 

We may, occasionally, ask you for further information about you as part of online surveys or if you enter any competition, contest or promotional 

Use of Cookies 

We use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize our pages, or register with the Site, a cookie helps us to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This saves you time and simplifies your use of the Site. When you return to the Site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the features that you No personally identifiable information is collected through the use of cookies. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Site. 

Security 

Your personal data will be held on our secure server located in the The Site is equipped with the latest security devices/firewalls. 

Third Party Sites 

The Site contains links to other websites, and you should be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices on any other website. 

Your information 

If you wish to know what information we hold on you, please contact us. We will only send this information to the e-mail address we have on file, unless you send us your postal address and request us to send the information to you at your postal An administrative charge as applicable at the time will be made for providing any such information that we hold about you. 

Should you request details of the information that we hold about you we may require proof of We also reserve the right to refuse to provide visitors with a copy of their personal information, but we will give reasons for such refusal. 

If you request us to remove your personal information from our database or you wish us to amend or change the information we hold about you on our database, we will remove or amend any such information on your request. 

Contact Us 

You may change and modify the information you have previously provided to us or otherwise contact us, as Send an e-mail to us at [ info@steelguru.com ](mailto:info@steelguru.com)   
Visit our URL at www.steelguru.com and log into the site.   
Send a letter to **Major & Minor Exims Pvt Ltd, 704B, Millennium Plaza, Sushant Lok I, Gurgaon 122002, Haryana, India **
